import { MCQuestionType, TFQuestionType } from "../types";

export const easyMC: MCQuestionType[] = [
  {
    question: "Who is often referred to as 'The King' in the NBA?",
    choices: ["Kobe Bryant", "LeBron James", "Michael Jordan", "Kevin Durant"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team drafted Shaquille O'Neal with the first overall pick in the 1992 NBA Draft?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Orlando Magic",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Golden State Warriors",
    ],
    correct: "Orlando Magic",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team is known as the 'Lob City' due to their highlight-reel alley-oops?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Clippers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most points scored in a single NBA game with 100 points?",
    choices: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Larry Bird",
    ],
    correct: "Wilt Chamberlain",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is known as the 'Splash Brother' alongside Stephen Curry on the Golden State Warriors?",
    choices: [
      "Klay Thompson",
      "Draymond Green",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Andre Iguodala",
    ],
    correct: "Klay Thompson",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player is famous for his 'Sky Hook' shot?",
    choices: [
      "Larry Bird",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Tim Duncan",
    ],
    correct: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
  },
  {
    question: "Who holds the record for the most assists in NBA history?",
    choices: ["Steve Nash", "John Stockton", "Chris Paul", "Jason Kidd"],
    correct: "John Stockton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the official height of an NBA basketball hoop from the floor?",
    choices: ["10 feet", "11 feet", "9 feet", "12 feet"],
    correct: "10 feet",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player is often called 'The Answer'?",
    choices: ["Allen Iverson", "Reggie Miller", "Tracy McGrady", "Ray Allen"],
    correct: "Allen Iverson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which team did Michael Jordan play for when he made his famous 'Flu Game' appearance in the NBA Finals?",
    choices: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Detroit Pistons",
    ],
    correct: "Chicago Bulls",
  },
  {
    question: "Which player is known for his 'Dream Shake' move in the post?",
    choices: [
      "Charles Barkley",
      "Tim Duncan",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
    ],
    correct: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the regulation game time duration for an NBA game?",
    choices: ["30 minutes", "48 minutes", "60 minutes", "90 minutes"],
    correct: "48 minutes",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the below NBA teams is often associated with the 'Malice at the Palace' brawl in 2004?",
    choices: [
      "New York Knicks",
      "Indiana Pacers",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
    ],
    correct: "Indiana Pacers",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time leading scorer in NBA history?",
    choices: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team drafted Kevin Garnett in 1995?",
    choices: [
      "Minnesota Timberwolves",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
    ],
    correct: "Minnesota Timberwolves",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA player is known for his 'Greek Freak' nickname?",
    choices: [
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Kristaps Porzingis",
      "Luka Dončić",
      "Nikola Jokić",
    ],
    correct: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA team is famous for its 'Showtime' era in the 1980s?",
    choices: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Miami Heat",
    ],
    correct: "Los Angeles Lakers",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most triple-doubles in NBA history?",
    choices: [
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Oscar Robertson",
      "Larry Bird",
    ],
    correct: "Russell Westbrook",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who won the NBA Rookie of the Year award in the 2020-2021 season?",
    choices: [
      "LaMelo Ball",
      "Anthony Edwards",
      "Tyrese Haliburton",
      "James Wiseman",
    ],
    correct: "LaMelo Ball",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player is known for his nickname 'The Brow' due to his distinctive unibrow?",
    choices: [
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Kawhi Leonard",
      "Jimmy Butler",
      "Damian Lillard",
    ],
    correct: "Anthony Davis",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team famously had the 'Bad Boys' era in the late 1980s?",
    choices: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Detroit Pistons",
    ],
    correct: "Detroit Pistons",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most three-pointers made in a single NBA season?",
    choices: ["Stephen Curry", "Ray Allen", "Klay Thompson", "James Harden"],
    correct: "Stephen Curry",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player is known as 'The Admiral' and spent his entire career with the San Antonio Spurs?",
    choices: ["Tim Duncan", "David Robinson", "Karl Malone", "Chris Webber"],
    correct: "David Robinson",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team is associated with the 'We Believe' era during the 2006-2007 season?",
    choices: [
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    correct: "Golden State Warriors",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time leader in steals in NBA history?",
    choices: [
      "Scottie Pippen",
      "Gary Payton",
      "John Stockton",
      "Michael Jordan",
    ],
    correct: "John Stockton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player is known for his nickname 'The Worm' due to his rebounding prowess?",
    choices: ["Dennis Rodman", "Kevin Garnett", "Chris Bosh", "Paul Pierce"],
    correct: "Dennis Rodman",
  },
  {
    question: "Which team is often referred to as the 'Dubs' by their fans?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Philadelphia 76ers",
    ],
    correct: "Golden State Warriors",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is known as 'Mr. Big Shot' for his clutch performances in the NBA?",
    choices: ["Paul Pierce", "Chauncey Billups", "Tony Parker", "Ray Allen"],
    correct: "Chauncey Billups",
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first overall pick in the 2018 NBA Draft?",
    choices: [
      "Deandre Ayton",
      "Luka Dončić",
      "Marvin Bagley III",
      "Trae Young",
    ],
    correct: "Deandre Ayton",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA team is associated with the 'Grit and Grind' era?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Clippers",
      "Oklahoma City Thunder",
      "Memphis Grizzlies",
      "Portland Trail Blazers",
    ],
    correct: "Memphis Grizzlies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who won the NBA MVP award in the 2019-2020 season while playing for the Milwaukee Bucks?",
    choices: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Anthony Davis",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
      "Kawhi Leonard",
    ],
    correct: "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA player is known for his nickname 'The Process'?",
    choices: [
      "Ben Simmons",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "De'Aaron Fox",
      "Jaren Jackson Jr.",
    ],
    correct: "Joel Embiid",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA team won six championships in the 1990s with Michael Jordan?",
    choices: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "San Antonio Spurs",
    ],
    correct: "Chicago Bulls",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the most blocks in a single NBA game with 17 blocks?",
    choices: [
      "Dikembe Mutombo",
      "Elmore Smith",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Manute Bol",
    ],
    correct: "Elmore Smith",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA team is known as the 'Bulls'?",
    choices: ["Chicago", "Miami", "New York", "Los Angeles"],
    correct: "Chicago",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA team's mascot is a green leprechaun?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Houston Rockets",
    ],
    correct: "Boston Celtics",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is known as 'The Mailman' in the NBA?",
    choices: [
      "Charles Barkley",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Karl Malone",
      "Tim Duncan",
    ],
    correct: "Karl Malone",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which NBA player won the 2020 NBA Finals MVP while playing for the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    choices: ["LeBron James", "Anthony Davis", "Jimmy Butler", "Kawhi Leonard"],
    correct: "LeBron James",
  },
  {
    question: "Which NBA team won the 2021 NBA Championship?",
    choices: [
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
    ],
    correct: "Milwaukee Bucks",
  },
];

export const easyTF: TFQuestionType[] = [
  {
    question: "Michael Jordan is often referred to as 'His Airness.'",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Larry Bird played his entire NBA career with the Boston Celtics.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The NBA is the only major professional sports league in North America that does not have a salary cap.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "Wilt Chamberlain scored 100 points in a single NBA game.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "The Phoenix Suns have never won an NBA Championship.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Shaquille O'Neal was known for his excellent free-throw shooting.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "The Toronto Raptors are the only Canadian team in the NBA.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The New York Knicks play their home games at Madison Square Garden.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar is the all-time leading scorer in NBA history.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Dennis Rodman won multiple NBA championships with the Los Angeles Lakers.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Los Angeles Clippers have more NBA Championships than the Los Angeles Lakers.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "The NBA Finals is a best-of-seven series.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Boston Celtics and Los Angeles Lakers have one of the most famous rivalries in NBA history.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term 'Triple-Double' in basketball refers to a player recording ten or more points, rebounds, and assists in a game.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Detroit Pistons are often associated with their 'Bad Boys' era in the 1990s.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Vince Carter, a legendary NBA player, was known for his high-flying dunks.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The 'Hack-a-Shaq' strategy involved intentionally fouling Shaquille O'Neal to send him to the free-throw line.",
    correct: "True",
  },
  {
    question: "The NBA's shot clock lasts for 30 seconds.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "The San Antonio Spurs have never won an NBA championship.",
    correct: "False",
  },
  {
    question: "The Los Angeles Lakers' colors are purple and gold.",
    correct: "True",
  },
];
